Ana Chkhaidze: Okay, call me when you're done. Okay?
Ana Chkhaidze: Hi. So when doing the experiment
Ana Chkhaidze: at first, st the flashing lights, they weren't so fast or well, the screen was flashing red, too. I'm not so sure what else.
Ana Chkhaidze: but it wasn't so fast and
Ana Chkhaidze: specifically, when I was looking in the middle of the screen. It did feel like the screen was coming forward in a way, and it felt like the screen was expanding, and it was becoming bigger.
Ana Chkhaidze: Something else that I did notice was sometimes the at the top.
Ana Chkhaidze: I like. I thought that I was. It looked like there was triangles, triangles facing down.
Ana Chkhaidze: But another visual that I did see was, if I was very focused specifically on one
Ana Chkhaidze: like I guess I could say the center when I was spoken on the send. In the center I noticed a red dot, and if I were to move my eyes
Ana Chkhaidze: that red dot would go there as well. But then it ended up disappearing.
Ana Chkhaidze: Something else, something else visually that I did notice, which
Ana Chkhaidze: was a little bit before I noticed the triangles at the top was if, when the the screen was flashing.
Ana Chkhaidze: I saw a 3 points
Ana Chkhaidze: to like make a triangle in the middle. But this time the triangle, it seemed like it was expanding. So it started off small, and then it became bigger. I only noticed that 3 times, and it was only that one time that I saw it.
Ana Chkhaidze: Let me see, I think one more thing that I did remember was.
Ana Chkhaidze: it looked like I'm not so sure how to explain. But
Ana Chkhaidze: the closest explanation I would have would be like the.
Ana Chkhaidze: It was oval shaped, and it was expanding, so it was becoming longer.
Ana Chkhaidze: I did notice that a few times again towards the middle.
Ana Chkhaidze: One last thing that I noticed throughout the experiment.
Ana Chkhaidze: Oh, yeah, sorry, since I had mentioned already the triangles at the top. That was the 1st instance that I saw them, but
Ana Chkhaidze: as the experiment continued, it got to a point where only
Ana Chkhaidze: 3 sides of the computer had those triangles. So my right, my left side, and the top had those triangles that were facing inwards.
Ana Chkhaidze: I I wouldn't say there are triangles, but
Ana Chkhaidze: to me it just seemed like
Ana Chkhaidze: it was the red screen that was flashing, but the outer edges
Ana Chkhaidze: were black, or there were black triangles.
Ana Chkhaidze: I think that was everything that I did see in the experiment. I'm trying to recall if I saw another visual.
Ana Chkhaidze: but for the most part it was just those main ones that I mentioned, the triangles at the top, and then, as well as on the side, and the triangle that was in the middle, and it expanded the oval.
Ana Chkhaidze: and I believe there is one more.
Ana Chkhaidze: But I can't really recall, or if I mentioned it. But yeah, that was everything. Thank you.
Ana Chkhaidze: I'm done.
Ana Chkhaidze: I mean, okay, perfect.